Guide to the Craig Wirth broadcast journalism audio-visual collection 1903-1990s, bulk 1950s-1990s
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
Craig Wirth broadcast journalism audio-visual collection
1903-1990s, bulk 1950s-1990s
University of Utah Libraries, Special Collections Audio Visual Archives Special Collections 295 South 1500 East Salt Lake City, Utah 84112-0860 (801) 581-8864
A0355
Wirth, Craig
64 16mm films, 331 U-Matic videcassettes, 2097 Betacam videocassettes, 82 VHS videocassettes, 1 MII videocassette, 21 Hi-8 videocassettes, 2 2-inch videocassettes, 1 1-inch videocassette, 8 reel-to-reel audiotapes, 4 audiocassettes and 4 phonograph records.
The Craig Wirth broadcast journalism audio-visual collection (1950s-1990s) contains numerous television news reports and documentaries made by Wirth during his long career in the television news industry. Items in the collection represent Wirth's career as a broadcast journalist in Salt Lake City, Utah, Los Angeles, California, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, and New York, New York and includes raw footage, research and source videos and completed works.
Biographical Note
Craig Brandon Wirth (b.1952) was born and raised in Montana. He received a Bachelor of Arts degree (BA) in Broadcast Journalism from the University of Utah in 1974, and a Masters of Arts degree (MA) in Urban Affairs Journalism from the University of Wisconsin in 1976. He has worked in many capacities in broadcast journalism, primarily as a feature reporter, at broadcasting stations in Salt Lake City (KCPX-TV, KUTV, KTVX-TV), Milwaukee (WTMJ AM-TV), New York (WOR-TV), and Los Angeles (KCBS-TV, KCAL-TV). He was a feature reporter on ABC's Good Morning America. He also has worked in cable broadcasting. He was a Los Angeles Bureau Reporter on CNBC. He was a Traveling Correspondent and Co-Host of American Entrepreneur for the Financial News Network. He was the Host and Co-Executive Producer for Famous Footsteps on the Travel Channel. In recognition of his outstanding feature reporting and writing, Craig Wirth has been nominated for seven New York and Los Angeles Emmy Awards, winning four, two for his 1985 feature Why New Jersey Has No State Song, one for a 1987 feature Turkeys, and one for a 1985 feature Punk Hair Cut. He also won four ABC Affiliates Americana Feature Contest Awards, and four Ace National Cable Awards, two for Best Program Host (American Entrepreneur) in 1990 and 1991, and two for Best Documentary (Rubles to Riches and Berlin Reborn) in 1990. He was the University of Utah Department of Communications "Outstanding Alumni" of 1992, and the University of Wisconsin Journalism School's "Outstanding Young Alumni" of 1986. He received the California Associated Press Mark Twain Award in Writing in 1986. He was an instructor at the University of Utah and Westminster College (1977-1981), a Visiting Lecturer in Broadcast Journalism at the University of Wisconsin (1983), and a Senior Lecturer in Journalism at the University of Southern California (1988-1990). Craig Wirth co-owned and served as President of Wirth/Salomon Productions of New York City, and also co-owned KCNY Radio of Moab (1978-1987).
The Craig Wirth broadcast journalism audio-visual collection (1960s-1990s) contains numerous television news reports and documentaries made by Wirth during his long career in the television news industry. Items in the collection represent Wirth's career as a broadcast journalist in Salt Lake City, Utah, Los Angeles, California, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, and New York, New York and includes raw footage, research and source videos and completed works.
The materials are arranged by accession date. The original 1998 donation is followed by the 2002 addendum. Some materials are grouped by subject matter or format type.
Materials must be used on-site; no use of original material, access copies will be made available for viewing. Five business days advanced notice required. Access to parts of this collection may be restricted under provisions of state or federal law, condition of the material, or by donor.
See also the Craig Wirth photograph collection (P0527)and papers (Accn 1310).
KUTV (Television station: Salt Lake City, Utah); KTVX (Television station: Salt Lake City, Utah); Salt Lake City (Utah); Television broadcasting of news--Utah; Journalism; Moving Images; Moving images
- 1998 donation
  - (Box 1)
    - Fall of communism, 1989,90; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1-41)
      Russia, Berlin Wall, Mikhail Gorbachev
  - (Box 2)
    - Unidentified videocassettes, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 42-44)
    - Unidentified videocassettes, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 45-51)
    - KTVX master story tape, 1988 March 30-April 28; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 52)
      Clowns (4/28/88, 2:13)
      School Orchestra (4/20/88, 1:56)
      Night Cop (3/30/88, 3:08)
      City County Building (4/06/88, 2:13)
      Midway Inn (4/13/88, 2:20)
      Camp (4/27/88, 2:03)
    - Guiding Light: A Celebration, 1987 February 11; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 53)
      Soap opera special
    - CBS Early Morning newsreel, 1986 March 11; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 54)
    - Craig Wirth USA, 1989; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 55)
    - Dream Living series, 1987; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 56)
    - Dream Living series part 5, 1987 February; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 57)
    - Big John, 1987 May; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 58)
    - Lancaster organ music, 1987 May 12; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 59)
    - Animal 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 60)
    - Max Headroom, undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 61)
  - (Box 3)
    - Blind Art, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 62-64)
      Treemont, Ogden art for blind students
    - Puerto Rico, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 65-69)
      Doree, Puerto Rico, Saint makers, rain forest footage, El Yungue
    - Petting farm in Utah County, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 70-72)
    - Juggling in Salt Lake City, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 74-75)
    - Juggling in Los Angeles, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 76)
    - Zoo babies; Olympus Junior High, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 77)
    - Silver City Press, Nex Mexico, 1990s; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 78-80)
    - On the Map: Phila, New Orleans, North Carolina, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 81-83)
    - Lighthouse, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 84-87)
      Upper Peninsula Michiga, Lake Superior
    - Space Needle, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 88-91)
    - Roller coasters, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 92-96)
    - Roller coasters, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 197)
    - Golfing in Florida, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 198)
  - (Box 4)
    - Unidentified films, undated; 16mm film (Reel 99-115)
    - Urban Transportation: Madison, Wisconsin, 1975; 16mm film (Reel 116-119)
      Master's thesis documentary
      A-B-roll full coad sand
    - Unidentified audiotapes, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 120-123)
    - Unidentified audiocassette, undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 124)
    - Home movies: mother, camerio, puppy, 1969; 16mm film (Reel 125-126)
    - Salt Lake City "Finger Lickin' Cops", 1970; 16mm film (Reel 127)
      Kentucky Fried Chicken, police
    - State Street at night, Salt Lake City, 1972; 16mm film (Reel 128)
    - Artificial heart at University of Utah: cow subject, 1962; 16mm film (Reel 129)
    - Orme's Story; High water in Great Salt Lake, undated; 16mm film (Reel 130)
    - 747 airplane flies into Salt Lake City, undated; 16mm film (Reel 131)
    - Price coal mine, undated; 16mm film (Reel 132)
    - Aba footage, Utah's stars, 1970; 16mm film (Reel 133-134)
    - Orme's report, undated; 16mm film (Reel 135)
    - Garrett, Montana ghost town, 1974; 16mm film (Reel 136)
    - Small Chance Gulch, Montana, 1974; 16mm film (Reel 137)
    - Food preparation at Hotel Utah, undated; 16mm film (Reel 138)
    - Plane graveyard in Tucson, Arizona, 1976; 16mm film (Reel 139)
      World War II aircraft
    - Herb, undated; 16mm film (Reel 140)
      One man newscast in Moab, Utah
    - Roy Clark and the Osmonds, undated; 16mm film (Reel 141)
    - Moab Water, 1976; 16mm film (Reel 142)
      Making of a rapid
    - Southern Utah footage, undated; 16mm film (Reel 143)
  - (Box 5)
    - Sonny Groso, French Connection cop, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 144-149)
    - Veterinarian in Upper Peninsula Michigan, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 150-152)
    - Female entrepreneurs: horseshoeing in Silver City, New Mexico, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 153-154)
    - Wold oil, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 155-158)
    - Female wrestlers, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 159)
    - KCBS: Police helicopters in Los Angeles, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 160-162)
    - Hialeah Race Track, Florida, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 163-164)
    - American Fork, Utah cops best dressed in United States of America, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 165)
    - Female entrepreneurs: Frieda's Fruit, California, 1989; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 166-167)
    - Disney collections archives, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 168)
    - KCBS: Life of a turkey, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 169)
      Emmy winner
    - CBS News: bug and spider provider for filmmakers, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 170)
    - California mud baths, 1987; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 171)
    - California mud baths, 1987; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 172)
    - Old cars, 1987; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 173-174)
    - Old cars, 1987; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 175)
    - Oil man, 1987; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 176)
      Oil well caretaker in California
    - WOR New York: Pumpkin Tape, 1984; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 177)
  - (Box 6)
    - Gondola, Indiana; Jacksonville, Florida, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 178-180)
    - William Clark, Clark Manson, Anaconda Mine Company, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 181-183)
    - Cheese plant in Mt Horeb, Wisconsin, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 184-187)
    - Seattle fish market, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 188-189)
    - Farm agent in Great Falls, Montana, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 190-191)
    - Backdraft story - Universal Pictures Theme Park, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 192)
    - Virgelle Ferry over Missouri River in Vergelle, Minnesota, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 193-194)
    - Episode of American Entrepreneur, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 195)
    - Salt Lake Golden Eagles hockey - Zamboni, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 196)
    - Country Craig; Wirth in the Army, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 197)
      Country western music
    - KTVX weather tape, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 198)
    - Country Craig; Girls baseball in Salt Lake City, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 199)
  - (Box 7)
    - Car wash, service station., undated; MII videocassette (Cassette 200)
    - The Super Bowl shuffle, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 201)
    - Bill Moyers: Reel world of news, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 202)
    - Our world, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 203)
    - Railroad, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 204)
    - "Utah Man", 1903; 1939; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 205)
      Recorded in 1903 by the original Deseret Academy Band.
      Recorded in 1939 by the Notre Dame Glee Club.
    - 60 of Southern California's finest single women, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 206)
    - Frank Fara, undated; Phonograph record (Disc 207)
      The Saga of Diamondfield Jack
      Donner Pass
    - Blue Suede Shoes, undated; Phonograph record (Disc 208)
    - Nitty Gritty Dirt Band, undated; Phonograph record (Disc 209)
      Cosmic Cowboy
    - The Southlanders, undated; Phonograph record (Disc 210)
      Whispering
      Davie
    - Unidentified audiotape, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 211)
  - (Box 8)
    - Location shots, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 212-222)
      Big Sky, Simi Valley, Laird Studio, Little Flouse, Dog Star Ranch
    - Soap operas, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 223-235)
      Young and the Restless and Guiding Light
    - Luxury train, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 236-241)
    - KTVX: Arnold's Mobile Gym, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 242-245)
    - Polo, lawn bowling, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 246-249)
    - Polo, lawn bowling, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 250)
    - Harbor master of Los Angeles, 1986; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 251)
    - Raw footage about B-17 and B-24 bombers, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 252)
    - Judge Wapner, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 253-254)
    - CNBC: Real story on Halloween masks in Los Angeles, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 255)
    - Aerial shots of Hollywood, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 256)
  - (Box 9)
    - Young and the Restless soap opera, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 257-268)
    - House series; Soap opera series, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 269-271)
    - Tower at KCBS in Montana, Mount Vision, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 272-273)
    - Glen Ivey Mus Massage, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 274-276)
    - Horse psychic, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 277-279)
    - Los Angeles police helicopter, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 280)
    - Bug movie props, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 281)
    - Doggie stars, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 282)
    - Sewage tour, Pocwhylur Beach, Los Angeles, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 283-285)
    - Location shooting, Zuma Beach, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 286)
    - Camp Hollywood, camp for urban children, Griffith Park Los Angeles, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 287)
    - Quiet Whitter - earthquake of Los Angeles, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 288)
    - KCBS audition reel, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 189)
      Studio, turkeys, Avalon organ
      Led to job at KCAL
  - (Box 10)
    - RKO sales presentation, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 190-193)
    - Luigi, a one man band; Wirth anchors the news, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 194-196)
    - Vaudeville performs, get together lunches in Manhattan, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 197-199)
    - Mail-order advertisements, comic books, Scientific American, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 200-201)
    - Raw footage of Helena and Butte, Montana, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 202-205)
    - Anaconda Stacks destruction, Great Falls, Montana, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 206-210)
    - University of Wisconsin college hockey, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 211-214)
    - Fabulous Freebers - WWF wrestling, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 215-217)
    - Dodger symphony, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 218-221)
      Rapid Brooklyn Dodgers fans in New York
    - Avalon organ on Catalina Island raw footage, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 222)
    - Junk store in Butte, Montana, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 223)
    - King Kong RKO story, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 224-225)
    - Wirth gets a hair-perm, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 226)
  - (Box 11)
    - London, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 227)
      Darts, changing of the guard
    - 747 airplane flies into Salt Lake City, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 228)
    - Wirth At War raw footage, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 229)
    - Airport footage: Mormon Tabernacle Choir leaves for Brazil, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 230)
    - KUTV: Old trains and Big Boy engines, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 231)
    - Bone phone, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 232)
      Bone, Idaho: last community to get telephone service in the United States
    - Country Craig; Christmas shopping; inversion story, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 233)
    - Utah State University professor; music with balloons; 3-year-old drumming prodigy; egg investigation; movie prop collection, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 234)
  - (Box 12)
    - Unidentified edit tapes, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 235-236)
    - Unidentified KUTV tape: Wirth 3, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 237)
    - Unidentified KCBS tape, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 238)
    - Unidentified WOR-TV tapes, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 239-241)
    - Wirth Watching, 1988 May; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 242)
    - Wirth Watching: circus, October 16; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 243)
    - Edit tape 10, 1981 January 29-February 09; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 244)
      Brigham (1/29/81, 2:05)
      Valentine (2/04/81, 1:27)
      Sugarless (1:32)
      Dog dress up (2/09/81, 1:54)
    - Old ranch house: Joe's ranch, 1982 December 09-10; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 245-247)
    - Helena 2, 6, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 248-249)
      Hockey
    - Chopper, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 250-251)
      Helicopter footage, possibly Utah's west desert
    - Le Phant II, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 252)
    - Square dance II, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 253)
      Baseball
    - Wrestling, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 254)
    - Fort Lee stills, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 255)
    - Volcano, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 256)
    - Good Morning America 2, 1988 October 17; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 257)
    - Opening day at Yankee Stadium, 1984 April 10; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 258)
  - (Box 13)
    - WOR New York: Rockettes at Radio City Music Hall, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 259-260)
    - WOR New York: Blimp over New York City, 1983; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 261-262)
    - NBC bloopers, 1982; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 263-264)
    - KUTV Salt Lake City: Joe's Ranch, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 265-266)
    - WOR New York: Thanksgiving gridlock, 1983; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 267)
    - KCBS Los Angeles: Footage of the sun, 1987; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 268)
    - WOR New York: Harrod's department store, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 269)
    - KUTV Salt Lake City: Bountiful flood, 1983; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 270)
    - KUTV Salt Lake City: Presidential visits to Utah (Carter), 1978; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 271)
    - KUTV Salt Lake City: Butte, Montana footage, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 272-273)
    - KUTV Salt Lake City: Circuit skiing in New Jersey, 1982; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 274)
    - KUTV Salt Lake City: University of Wisconsin stories of students, 1983; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 275)
    - KUTV Salt Lake City: Montana State Prison story, 1982; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 276)
    - Big Boy trains, 1982; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 277)
    - KUTV Salt Lake City: Mirror Lake (Uinta Mountans), 1980; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 278)
    - KUTV Salt Lake City: Japanese country singer, 1976; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 279)
    - KUTV Salt Lake City: Mulching, killing Christmas trees, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 280)
    - KUTV Salt Lake City: Highland High TV class, 1978; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 281)
    - KUTV Salt Lake City quotes mail order for NBC over night, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 282)
    - CNN: Barney equestrian cop, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 283)
    - KUTV Salt Lake City: Political campaign pens, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 284)
    - KUTV Salt Lake City: Senior citizens musical band, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 285)
    - WOR New York: Political story, 1984; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 286)
    - WOR New York: Story of Ellis Island; remodeling the Statue of Liberty, 1985; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 287)
    - KUTV Salt Lake City: Kegger party for the Universary of Montana Library, musical guest star Bonnie Raitt, 1976; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 288)
    - WOR New York: Music track for Valentine's Day, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 289)
    - WOR New York: New York City World's Fair in 1939 and 1960; televisions in World War II, 1984; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 290-291)
    - WOR New York: 50th Anniversary Grover's Mill, New Jersey War of the Worlds, 1988; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 292)
    - WOR New York: Great political advertising, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 293)
  - (Box 14)
    - Old Ford automobiles in Montana, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 294-295)
    - Political advertising, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 296-297)
    - WOR New York: Circus in New York City, 1984; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 298)
    - Godzilla comes to Salt Lake City in Marvel Comics, 1976; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 299)
    - KUTV Salt Lake City: Stunt man in Utah, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 300)
    - Oyster boat in Delaware Bay, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 301)
    - WOR New York: Cape May, New Jersey and Route 9, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 302)
    - KUTV Salt Lake City: Osmond Hour with guest stars Roy Clark and Cheryl Tiggs, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 303)
    - PM Magazine promo tape, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 304)
  - (Box 15)
    - Unidentified KTVX tapes, 1988-1989; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 305-306)
    - Unidentified WOR tape, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 307)
    - Unidentified KCBS tape, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 308)
    - Craig Wirth recent work 103, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 309)
    - Animal, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 310-312)
      Animal tapes 2-3, Animal election
    - Wirth dubs, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 313)
    - CBS news, December 01; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 314)
    - Early morning news, May 29; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 315)
    - KCBS: 6PM aircheck, September 17; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 316)
    - Wirth Waching stories, 1976-1977; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 317)
      Promo
      Gargoyles
      Sportscaster covering City Hall
      One man airport in Montana
      World's largest beer kegger
      Cereal
      Diamondfield Jack
      One man newscast
      What Newswatch 2 doesn't show
      Airplane graveyard
      Boring life
      Telephone calls
      The ten least significant events of 1977
      Japanese country western singer
    - KCBS: Wirth look-back, 1983; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 318)
    - Pay Pacific, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 319)
    - Generics, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 320)
  - (Box 16)
    - Miller Lite television reunion, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 321)
    - Billy Rhodes interview, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 322)
      silent film star with Lasky Studios
    - Breakfast club for senior citizens; interview with Gene Bell, 1987; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 323-325)
    - Hollywood stories, 1988; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 326)
    - KHJ Los Angeles: Nude liquor laws, 1989; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 327)
    - Animal stories, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 328)
    - National Car Rental: old cars for rent, 1987; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 329)
    - Dodger Stadium employees; the horse riders, 1986; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 330)
    - Avalon production tape, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 331)